翻译：小布拿拿      红豆包      斯人
《开心汉堡店》第五季第九集
翻译&校对&总监：Iz
后期：斯人     时间轴：深夏桃子
我美丽的杀虫剂
除虫害公司
更多动画  就在@欧美动漫汉化军团
极速恶魔
等我们玩完卡丁车回家
Mom and Dad might not recognize us
老爸老妈估计都认不出我们了
when we get back from go-karting.
因为我们的头发会像这样
'Cause our hair will be like this.
我们的脸会像这样
And our faces will be like this!
我们的小鸡鸡像这样
And our penises will be like this.
你们看不到我变成啥样了  但很惊人
You can't see what I'm doing, but it's pretty great.
请拿三张儿童票
Three youth tickets, please.
抱歉  跑道今天关闭了
Sorry, track's closed for the rest of the day.
有比赛
League racing.
-什嘛  -可我踩了那么久的脚踏车过来
- What?! - What? - But I pedaled all this way
就是为了体验下踩油门的感觉啊
to put the pedal to the metal.
你们改天再来吧
You'll have to come back another time.
可以看看网上的日程表
Perhaps check the online calendar
我上网都是看树懒
If I'm online, I'm looking at sloths.
哇
Mama like.
好快  我好好奇
They're fast, and I'm curious.
去他的普通卡丁车
Screw regular go-karting.
我想开那样的
I want to do that.
想进车队的小孩多了去了
Every kid wants to be in league racing.
排队去吧
Get in line.
好吧  上哪儿排队
Okay, where's the line?
你真幽默  亲爱的
Funny, honey.
要想上跑道  就得去弄辆赛车
The only way to join the circuit is to get a kart.
没问题  上哪儿弄
No problem. Where do we get one?
都是订做的  最少也得一千大洋
They're custom. They cost a grand, at least.
我在哪儿见过你
I know you from somewhere.
-你是皇颅岛的布莱斯对吗  -没错
- You're Bryce from Kingshead Island, aren't you? - Yep.
-太好了  还记得我们吗  -不记得
- Oh, yeah. Remember us? - Nope.
-真伤人  -真遗憾你们不能加入
- Ouch. - Too bad you won't be joining the league.
冶叱繁呦蚰忝侨悠咸迅煽隙ê苡腥?
It would've been fun chucking raisins at you as I blow by.
天哪  我可真恨他
Oh, my God, I hate him.
我很难恨一个朝我扔葡萄干的人
Hard to hate a guy who gives you raisins.
今日推荐汉堡三件套
Three burgers of the day.
你的朋友什么来历  泰迪
Who are your pals, Teddy?
他们是我在家酿酒用品店认识的
These guys are from the home brew supply shop.
我带他们来尝尝你们的汉堡
I brought 'em over here to try your burgers
配泰迪啤酒
with Teddy's Brewski.
泰迪啤酒是什么
What's Teddy's Brewski?
这是我自制的啤酒
It's the name of my home-brewed beer.
我过去叫它桶酒
I used to call it Bucket Brew,
因为我是在桶里
since that's where it ferments.
发酵的
In a bucket.
鉴于你是在桶里酿的
You know, it's just that you brewed it in a bucket.
当然安全了  酒有啥不安全的
Of course it's safe. It's alcohol.
不错吧
Right?
真可爱
so cute.
你的汉堡和他的啤酒真是相亲相爱呢
Your burgers and his beer are making little belly babies.
-咋了  -鲍勃
- What? - Oh, Bob.
-鲍勃  鲍勃  -什么  什么  什么
- Bob! Bob! - What what? What?
你应该卖我的啤酒
You should sell my beer!
-我们可以当合作伙伴  -什么
- We could be partners! - What?
泰迪  餐馆是不允许
Teddy, I-I don't think restaurants are allowed
卖自制啤酒的
to sell home-brewed beer.
谁会管啊
who's gonna care?
卫生检查员  酒精管理署  警察局
The health inspector, the Bureau of Alcohol, the police...
不被发现就好了嘛
So we won't get caught.
就像地下酒吧那样
We'll run it like a speakeasy.
我就扮演阿尔・卡彭  只不过有胸而已
I'll be like Al Capone with breasts.
美国黑社会罪犯
曾在美国禁酒令期间以贩卖私酒获取庞大利润
鲍勃  尝尝你的汉堡  再喝口我的啤酒
Come on, Bob, just taste your burger and then my beer.
配的上我的汉堡的啤酒
Well, it's pretty hard to pair my burgers
不多的说
with the right beer.
天哪
Oh, my God.
-不错吧  -天哪
- Right? - Oh, my God.
-太棒了  -他说很棒
- That's amazing. - It's amazing!
就这么办
Let's do it!
-就这么办  -太好了
- Let's do it! - Yes!
奇幻码头
如果卡丁车能为餐馆做广告
Maybe Mom and Dad would sponsor a go-kart
也许老爸老妈会赞助我们一辆
if it was advertising for the restaurant.
他们可是连自己电费单都赞助不起的人
They can't even sponsor their electric bill.
或许我们可以换个目标
Or maybe a sponsorship would work.
你好  费舍奥德先生
Hey, Mr. Fischoeder!
-我想你了  -该死
- I missed you. - Damn.
-你都去哪儿了  -到处转转
- Where have you been? - Oh, around.
只要你出资给我们赞助一辆卡丁车
How would you like to have semi-exclusive
就能享有一半的独家广告权 怎么样
advertising rights on a go-kart that you pay for?
我出资  听起来好奇怪
Me pay kids? That sounds weird.
这样吧  你们付我钱
How 'bout you pay me--
听起来舒服多了
that sounds better...
别啊
No.
等等  我还没说完
Hold on. I haven't finished.
在这当中选一辆
For one of these!
一辆故障的碰碰车
A broken-down bumper car?
搞不好你们可以把
Perhaps you kids can turn one
其中一辆改装成很棒的赛车呢
of these not go-karts into a very much go-kart.
有人在这里睡觉  费先生
Someone's sleeping back here, Mr. Fish.
那是我们的员工休息室
That's our employee lounge.
欧文  醒醒
Owen, wake up!
你看起来跃跃欲试嘛
You look like you've got something to prove.
伙计们  我想就是这辆了
Guys, I think this is the one.
那辆最贵了
that's the most expensive one.
我们出价三美金
We'll give you three bucks for it.
成交  除非你们想出八美金
Deal. Unless you want to make it eight dollars
再买一辆  免费赠送欧文
for a second bumper car, plus Owen,
随意使用
whom I will throw in for free.
-他能做什么  -鬼知道
- What can he do? - Lord knows.
还有待考察
It all remains to be seen.
他潜力巨大
He's a mass of potential.
现在就差一台割草机发动机了
Now all we need is a lawn mower engine.
或蒸汽发动机
Or a steam engine.
或摩托车发动机
Or a motorcycle engine.
我们得付多少钱  克里特
So how much is it gonna cost us, Critter?
我不能收你们的钱
Come on, I can't charge you guys.
我们的孩子在你们餐馆里出生
Our kid was born inside your restaurant.
零件就当有人帮你们付了
Plus, I think the parts will be donated,
你们懂的
if you catch my drift.
来吧  伙计们  我们把这老家伙给拆了
Come on, people, let's tear this old dog apart,
教给它新的计能
teach it new tricks!
贝尔彻赛车
一半是碰碰车  一半是卡丁车  酷毙
Half bumper car, half go-kart, all balls.
很好
Nice.
你们会把那些富家子弟打得落花流水
You're gonna bump those rich kids right off the track.
我们的零食呢
And how are we on snack storage?
妥妥的  就在这边
Chip clip right there on the side.
妥妥的  太好了
Chip clip! -Yeah.
驾驶的方法还是和碰碰车一样
Now, she's gonna handle like a bumper car.
方向盘很松  所以
The steering's real loose, so don't be afraid
急转什么的放心来
to whip that wheel around real good.
知道了知道了  只需要踩油门就行了
Yeah, yeah. You push the pedal and the thing goes.
真想让布莱斯看看这俩酷毙的座骑
Wait till Bryce gets a load of this sweet ride.
那是什么
What is that?
你嫉妒了吗
Are you jealous?
看着不像
It doesn't sound like you are,
到了赛场上你就会改变主意了
but you will be once we race against you.
你们没机会和我比
You're not gonna race against me.
什么意思
What are you talking about?
我在A队
I'm in A-league.
新车在B队
New cars start out in B-league.
你们得一直获胜才能升到A队
You got to win your way up to A-league.
你在开玩笑吗
Are you kidding me?
没有  我很认真的
Nope. I'm serious-ing you.
等我赢下皇颅岛大奖赛
I'll be winning the Kingshead Island Grand Prix
你们估计都还没搞清楚
when you're still figuring out
哪个是油门  哪个是刹车
which pedal is the gas and which is the brake.
中间那个又大又圆控制方向的东西呢
And the big round thing in the middle that steers it?
那是你老妈  噗
That's your mom. Burn.
你都从嘴里放屁的吗  那可是你的脸啊
Oh, that fart with a mouth? That's your face!
随你怎么说啦
Yeah, right.
选手们  离B队比赛开始还有十分钟
Drivers, ten minutes till the B-league race.
那是在说我们吧  咱去把B队打个落花流水
I guess that's us. Let's go tear up the B-league
然后冲爆布莱斯的排气管
so we can blow it out Bryce's tailpipe.
准备上场
Here we go.
祝我好运
Wish me luck out there.
等等  为啥要祝你们好运
Wait, what do you mean wish you luck?
-因为我来开车  -我以为是我来开
- 'Cause I'm driving. - I thought I was driving.
我还以为一致认为是我来开呢
I thought we all thought I was driving.
天哪
Oh, my God.
我们都没讨论过谁来开车吗
Did we not talk about who's gonna drive?
当然是我啊
It's obviously me.
还记得我摩托车游戏玩得多棒吗
But remember how good I was at that motorcycle arcade game?
不撞车才叫玩得棒好吗
The point is to not burst into flames.
严重反对
Strongly disagree.
蒂娜  你也好不到哪儿去
Tina, you're not much better.
记得你那次在停车场
Remember what happened
开车发生了什么吗
when you drove the car in the parking lot?
那次情况不同  是违规开车
That was different. That was dirty driving.
这次是合法的  卡丁车是正规又有趣的
This is legal. Go-karting is good clean fun.
只有用这个办法了
There's only one way to settle this.
-吉恩毛痣赛吗  -吉恩毛痣赛
- Gene's hairy mole? - Gene's hairy mole.
哎哟
Oh, boy.
对齐了
Hold 'em up.
好嘞  我是说
Yes! Uh, I mean...
随便啦  我来开车
Whatever. I'm the driver.
但是  这是团队荣誉
But, hey, it's all about the team.
对吧  亲们
Right, sibs?
好吧  很公平
Fair is fair, I guess.
加油
Go team.
很好  蒂娜  这才是团队精神
Yeah, Tina! That's the spirit!
你知道吗
And you know what,
你可以当我的递水妹
I want you to be my water girl out there.
怎么样
How does that sound?
从车手直接贬到递水妹么
Water girl instead of race kart driver?
我考虑考虑
Let me think about that.
我赢了  就是我们赢了
Hey, when I win this race, it'll be like we all won.
但主要是我  蒂  来点水喝
Especially me. T, give me a squirt.
喷岔了  你故意的吗
You missed. Did you do that on purpose?
不  这瓶子疯了  哎呀
No. What a crazy water bottle. Oh, whoops.
又来了  不好意思
It's doing it again. Oh, sorry. Hey!
这  这失控了
This is... this is crazy.
车手们  启动引擎
Drivers, start your engines.
那人能让旗子做任何事
That guy can make a flag do anything he wants.
但主要还是挥来挥去
But mostly flap around.
给点力啊  你这坨垃圾
Come on, you hunk of junk!
走直线  转弯啊  转弯
Go straight! Now turn! Turn!
你这是在转弯吗  另一边啊
You call that turning? The other way!
不错嘛  孩子
Pretty good, kid.
但你会"格斯"这套动作吗
But can you Gus?
真漂亮
It's beautiful!
为什么叫格斯
Why is it called Gus?
是以我的名字命名的
It's named after me.
我就叫格斯
My name is Gus.
很多人以为”格斯“是靠手腕
A lot of people think the Gus comes from the wrists.
其实不是  是靠这个
It doesn't. It comes from in here.
你的瓶子吗
Your flask?
是的  还有心
Yes. And the heart.
不用心  你只是在挥
Without heart, you're just waving a flag around
黏了块布的小木棍
at the end of a little stick.
以你的天赋  我看你够格
Hey, maybe you've got what it takes
当初级格斯实习生了
to be a junior-Gus-in-training.
我一生就等这句话了
I've waited my entire life to hear those exact words!
这碰碰卡丁车真垃圾
That bumper-kart is terrible.
我们用这玩意永远别想赢
We'll never win a race in that thing.
要是你有照克里特教的方法开
Well, we might if, you know,
没准我们能赢的
you drove it like Critter told us to.
什么意思
What's that supposed to mean?
也许不是车的问题
Maybe it's not the kart's fault
你把所有墙都给撞遍了  然后掉了个头
you slammed into all those walls and got turned around
往错的方向开了好久
and drove the wrong way for an embarrassing amount of time.
你觉得你能驾驭那玩意吗  你请
You think you can drive that thing? Be my guest.
溜一圈啊
Take a lap.
我们轻轻来慢慢来
We're gonna go nice and easy.
你领头  我跟上
You lead, I'll follow.
我知道你想撞上去但不准哦
I know you want to bump into stuff but you can't.
你现在是辆赛车
You're a race car now.
是个大车了  这就对了  极速先生
You're all grown-up. That's it, Mr. Speedy.
-看见了吗  -看什么
- See? - See what?
转弯呀  我没像你那样乱撞一通吧
How I took that turn instead of crashing like you did?
也许该由我
Maybe I should be the one
来担任贝尔彻队的车手
behind the wheel for Team Belcher?
蒂娜  听着  这是我第一次开
Tina, hello, it was my first race.
好嘛  闪开
Okay? Back off.
而且  我正大光明赢了吉恩毛痣赛
Besides, I won Gene's hairy mole fair and square.
所以别再讨论这个了
So let's speak of this no more.
可是  也许我能赢...
It's just, I could maybe win...
吉恩毛痣赛
Gene's hairy mole!
我知道  吉恩毛痣赛
I know. Gene's hairy mole.
-怎么样了  -好着呢
- How's it coming? - Great.
等这批好了
Once I'm done here,
我就从地下室再拿一批
I'm gonna bring up another batch from the basement.
用旧瓶子装家酿啤酒
Home brew in used bottles.
这地下酒吧的活干得越来越顺手了嘛
I think we're getting good at this speakeasy thing.
这小口小口的喝得我都快醉了
And all these sipsies are getting me tipsy.
有些瓶盖是我捶上去的
I had to hammer some of the caps back on
有些还动用了胶带  但是
and I used tape for a couple of 'em, but...
应该没人会发现的
I don't think anyone will notice.
请再来一瓶"啤酒"  眨眼
Another "beer" please? Wink.
再来一瓶普通啤酒吗
Another one of the beers we normally sell here?
好的  给你
Sure. Here you go.
刚开的哦
Live one!
他是应该说出"眨眼"这两个字
Is he supposed to say "wink"?
还是做眨眼这个动作
Or is he just supposed to wink?
我们都有做
Well, we've been doing both.
天哪  天哪  鲍鲍  调查员来了
Oh, God. Oh, God! Bobby, the G-men are here!
快像电影里那样把整个房间翻过来
Turn the whole room around like they do in the movies!
快点  去
Quick, go!
不  不  不是现在
Ugh, no, no. Not now.
泰迪  快离开这  快点  快点
Teddy, get out of here! Hurry. Hurry.
-雨果  -鲍勃
- Hugo! - Bob.
-罗恩  -鲍勃  -罗恩
- Ron. - Bob. - Ron!
这里有什么不对劲的地方  罗恩
Oh. What's wrong with this picture, Ron?
居然有顾客
There are actually customers in here!
对哦
Right.
闻起来
Smells...
有发酵的味道
yeasty.
我从没在这儿闻到过这种扑鼻的
I've never smelled this tangy...
酸酸的
sour...
发酵的味道
yeast here before.
那个  我们开始烤面包了
Well, we have started baking bread,
-你闻到的可能是发面团的味道  -对
- so maybe you're smelling the yeast from that. - Yeah.
-那面团在哪  鲍勃  -我们...
- And where is this yeasty bread, Bob? - Uh, we, uh...
我们丢掉了  味道不咋地  不好
we threw it away. It wasn't any good. No.
难吃  难吃  做的不好  所以
Terrible, terrible. It didn't come out, so...
这是我们第一次尝试
I mean, it was our first batch.
我们还...
You know? W-We're not...
我们哪有那么厉害  你知道的
Who are we? You know?
我们又不是面包专家
We're not bread experts.
面包
Bread.
雨果  你真不用下去的
Hugo, you really don't have to go down there!
好浓的酵母味
So yeasty.
好了  你别再说那个词了
Okay, you need to stop saying that word.
听着不舒服
It's making me uncomfortable.
真的吗  酵母  酵母  酵母
Oh, really? Yeasty, yeasty, yeasty.
我知道我怎么想的吗  鲍勃
You know what I think, Bob?
我觉得面包只是你掩盖真相的借口
I think the bread story is a cover for what you're really doing.
那真相是什么呢
And what would that be?
你在自己酿啤酒
You're brewing your own beer!
什么  真是搞笑  什么
What?! That's crazy. What?
真搞笑  啤酒
It's crazy. Beer.
你怎么这么说  谁在酿啤酒呢
Where would you get that? Who's brewing beer?
什么  什么  什么玩意
What are... What is... what is this?
-什么  他是谁啊  -什么啤酒
- What? Who is this guy? - Beer.
知道吗  唯一比做家酿啤酒
You know, the only thing worse than an idiot who makes
更蠢的就是卖家酿啤酒的餐馆老板
bacteria-infested home brew is a restaurant that serves it.
好吧  雨果  这里真没家酿啤酒
Well, Hugo, there's no home brew here,
检查完了吗
So are we done with the inspection?
差不多了
I suppose.
但我告诉你  鲍勃
But know this, Bob,
要是我发现你在卖自酿啤酒
if I find out you are selling bacteria beer,
你就等着三重打击吧
you're going to get the triple smack-down.
第一重  我会让你关门
Smack one, I shut you down.
第二重  酒类营业执照  没戏了
Smack two, beer and wine license? Gone.
第三重
Smack three?
告诉他们  罗恩
Tell 'em, Ron.
下地狱吧  鲍勃
You rot in hell, Bob!
走吧  罗恩
Let's go, Ron.
我会回来尝面包的  鲍勃
And I'll be back to try that bread, Bob.
很好  它会在这等你的  雨果
Great. 'Cause it's gonna be here, Hugo.
很好  我会带嘴来的
Oh, great! I'll bring my bread mouth!
我们的地下酒吧是不是得就此打住了
So I guess this means the speakeasy's over?
什么都没结束  泰迪
Nothing's over, Teddy.
雨果阻止不了我们
Hugo can't stop us.
谁知道怎么烤面包
All right, who knows how to bake bread?
挥呀挥呀挥  摇呀摇呀摇
Flutter, flutter, flutter. Shimmy, shimmy, shimmy.
再来一个切旗
And snap it off!
切得一手好旗嘛  吉恩
Hell of a snap-off, Gene.
是啊 但我摇得很烂
Yeah, but my shimmy was shabby.
我昨天看到你开那四不像了
I saw you drive that monstrosity the other day.
让我印象深刻  想散散步聊聊吗
It was impressive. Want to take a little walk and talk?
-我有个提议  -我有主了
- I have a proposition for you. - I'm taken.
这有点复杂
Well, it's complicated.
亲爱的  我要是想泡你  会让你知道的
Honey, if I was hitting on you, you'd know,
那时你会被吓到的
because you'd be terrified.
你就是在跟我搭讪
Trust me, you're hitting on me.
请跟我们来吧
Just come with us, please.
我叫沙夏  这是我的赛车队
My name is Sasha, and this is my racing team.
-你好  -你们好
- Hi. - Hi.
想不想当赛车手
So how'd you like to be a driver?
不行啊  我妹妹才是我们队的车手
Oh, I can't. My sister is our team's driver.
她光明正大地赢了驾驶权
She won the right to drive fair and square.
吉恩毛痣赛  我们用它来决定...
Gene's hairy mole. It's this thing we do with...
不必了  我没兴趣
Oh, it's okay. I don't need to know.
听着  我不是让你开那玩意儿
Listen, I'm not talking about you driving that thing.
我说的是这个
I'm talking about this.
我们的常驻车手埃迪又被拘留了
Eddy, our usual driver, is in detention again.
你要是今天能代表KIS出战
You'd be doing us a big favor
就是帮了我们一个大忙了
if you drove the K.I.S. Kart today.
-KISS[吻]么  -不  KIS
- "Kiss"? - No, K.I.S.
是皇颅岛飞车队的简写
It stands for Kingshead Island Speeders.
-我能叫它"吻"吗  -不行  听我说
- Can I call it "Kiss"? - No. Listen to me.
你将有机会驾驶真正的赛车
This is your chance to drive a real race kart,
还是在A队
in the A-league.
不是要一直获胜才能晋级到A队么
But I thought you had to win your way into the A-league.
关键在车
It's about the kart.
这辆车已经是A队的了
This kart is already in the A-league.
可为啥你们自己不开呢
But why don't you want to drive the car yourself?
开车谁都会  我要的是赢
Any kid can drive. I want to win.
你觉得我能赢么  在A队里
You think I can win? In A-league?
如果你开那个老爷车
If you can get that bumper-fart
都能在70秒内开完一圈
around the track in 70 seconds,
想想开这个会多快吧
imagine how fast you can go in this.
你加这台车搞不好能
You and this thing might actually have what it takes
把布莱斯从第一的位置上赶下来
to knock Bryce off the top spot.
他也早该被拉下来了
He deserves to be beaten, by the way.
他是个下流的车手
He's a dirty driver.
我们叫他"不乃斯"
We call him Not Nice Bryce.
不好说啊
I don't know.
碰碰卡丁车是我们姐弟一起做的
The bumper-kart is kind of a family project.
当然  你说得对
Oh, sure, of course, yeah.
你大可以继续
You can just keep squirting water
给你妹妹当个端茶送水的
into your sister's mouth if you want.
这是给你的最后一名奖牌
Here, I made you this last-place medal.
口香糖
It's gum.
干得漂亮  布莱斯
Good one, Bryce.
开玩笑  我最爱嚼过的口香糖
Joke's on you. I love old gum!
可以了  他走了
It's okay. He walked away.
蒂娜  你穿的什么啊
Tina, what are you wearing?
车手服
A driver's jumpsuit.
我们讨论过了  好吗
We've been through this, okay?
贝尔彻车队只有我一个赛车手
Belcher Racing only has one driver, and that's me.
我知道  我是为皇颅岛飞车队出战
I know. I'm driving for the Kingshead Island Speeders.
-什么  -我叫它"吻"车队
- What?! - I call it "Kiss."
你要背弃贝尔彻车队
You're abandoning Team Belcher?
你怎么能这么对我们
How can you do that to us?!
你就是贝尔彻家的贝内迪克特・阿诺德
You're like a Belcherdict-Arnold!
美国独立战争史上的中途变节将军
我的驾车技术在我们中最好
I was Team Belcher's best driver,
可你为了自己能开车
but you didn't care if we won
不管比赛的输赢
as long as you got to be the driver.
太疯狂了  你疯了
That's crazy. You're crazy.
脱下你的赛车服  拿起你的水瓶
Get out of that jumpsuit, get your water bottle
回休息站去
and get back in the pit.
我再也不要回去了
I'm never going back to the pit
除非那儿有冷气可以吹  有男生可以泡
unless the pit is a cool diner where teens hang out.
A队的比赛要开始了  我得走了
Look, the A-league race is about to start. I got to go.
你在A队
You're in A-league?!
是啊  很赞
Yeah, it's pretty cool.
如果获胜他们还会给你的车一个小花环
They give your go-kart a little wreath if you win.
了不起死了
Oh, wow! Isn't that great?
就是了不起啊  回见
It is pretty great. Bye!
-嘿  蒂娜  你还好么  -很好
- Hi, Tina. How are you doing? - Good.
你看上去有点僵硬啊  孩纸
'Cause you're looking a little stiff out there, kiddo.
谁在说话
Who's saying this?
沙夏  你头盔里有个无线电
Sasha. I'm on the radio inside your helmet.
我差点还以为你是
Oh, 'cause I thought for a second you were...
没什么  不能让你知道我在想什么
Oh, never mind. I'm not gonna tell you what I thought.
蒂娜  你开得像个送水妹
Tina, you're driving like a water girl.
拜托  放松点
Come on, cut it loose.
好的  好的  我只是需要
All right, all right, I just need
稍微熟悉一下车  你好呀
to get to know the car a little, I guess. Hello.
你和碰碰卡丁车有点不同呢
You feel different than the bumper-kart.
不过我一定也和你的老主人不一样吧
But I must feel different than your old driver,
因为我是个姑娘  反正别人是这么说的
'cause I have a girl butt, or so I'm told.
对了  我叫蒂娜
I'm Tina, by the way.
蒂娜  我要把你静音了
Tina, I'm gonna put you on mute.
好的
Okay.
你真棒
You did that really well.
转得漂亮  轮子
Nice turning, wheels.
方向盘  你也不错
And good job, steering wheel, too.
引擎  你也克尽己任
And, engine, you did your part.
第二名  我就知道
Second place! I knew it!
我就知道你是个赛车手
I knew you were a racer!
你奇奇怪怪自言自语的时候
I got a little worried when you were talking to yourself
我还有点担心  不过你成功了
and being really weird, but then you came through!
那就没事了
It's okay!
这次第二  下次打败布莱斯
This time second, next time beat Bryce.
蒂娜  能递给我张纸巾吗
Tina, can you pass me a napkin?
尽量别出卖它
And try not to betray it.
露易丝  麻烦递一下胡椒粉
Louise, please pass the pepper.
别把盐罐子撞坏了哦
And try not to crash it into the salt.
你怎么不想想胡椒是从哪儿来的
Why don't you try to remember where that pepper came from?
从这儿  从这间房子  从这个家
From here, from this apartment, from this family.
这就是胡椒的由来啊
So that's where pepper comes from.
姑娘们  你们俩给我停下
Girls, you two need to stop all this.
你们现在都是赛车手了
You're both go-kart drivers now.
你俩又不是对手  对吗
And you're not even racing against each other, right?
没错  我在A队
That's right. I'm in the A-league.
我跟你干上了  T
Well, I'm coming for you, T.
如果这个赛季我能在B队拿到冠军
If I finish the season in first place in the B-league,
我就能在皇颅岛大奖赛占据一席
then I get a spot in the Kingshead Island Grand Prix.
-是嘛  -没错
- You do? - Yup.
到时候我就能打败你了
And that's when I get to beat you.
那也得比赛
But you have to actually win races
才能拿冠军啊
to finish in first place.
也许你没完全弄明白
Maybe you didn't totally understand that.
没完了
Oh, keep it up.
我已经把你甩得远远的了
Way ahead of you. Literally.
听着  我知道有谣传说
Look, I know there's this rumor
蒂娜技术更好  而且我猜是你传出来的
that Tina's a better driver, and I think you started it,
但我俩这次要好好努力
but you and me are gonna work real hard,
我们要赢
and we're gonna win some races.
看起来我们要在大奖赛碰面了哦  老姐
Looks like I'll be seeing you at the Grand Prix, sis.
颁奖台上见
And I'll be seeing you from the first place podium.
当然  家里也会见  还有车里
Also, I'll see you at home, and also in the car,
我们应该会搭同一辆车来参加比赛
'cause we should probably carpool to the race.
得得  知道啦
Yup, yup, got it!
踩油门  出发咯
I hit the gas, and I drive away!
新鲜的面包都能给你烤得这么老
It's weird how you freshly baked the staleness
真是太奇怪了
right into them.
-这是家族秘方  -再来一瓶冰的  鲍勃
- It's-it's an old family secret. - Another cold one, Bob.
鲍勃  那个汉堡胚看着和这个不一样啊
Hey, Bob, that bun doesn't look like this bun, Bob.
你想忽悠我呢
You trying to screw me?
我要现烤汉堡胚
I want the fresh-baked buns.
这么说  你做汉堡不是用的这些胚咯
So, you're not using these buns on your burgers?
-太可疑了  格雷琴  -说
- Suspicious. Gretchen? - Move on.
我们做的这些胚是给
We're-we're making buns for,
-给谁  -是给
- For what? - Uh, the buns are for...
-给早餐用的  -没错
- For breakfast! - Yes.
我们要开始卖早餐了现在
We're gonna start breakfast now.
鲍勃店的早餐
Breakfast at Bob's.
我都等不及想要试试了
I can't wait to come by and try it.
六点  可以吗
6 A.M. Sound good?
我是说  我们还没讨论好
I mean, well, we haven't really talked
什么时候开始卖早饭  所以
about when we're opening yet, so...
那就六点见
Okay, see you at 6:00 then.
最好有香肠哦  鲍勃
And you better have sausages, Bob!
会有的
We'll have it!
皇颅岛赛车大奖赛
孩子们最近在干这个啊
So, this is what the kids have been up to?
我一点都没想到会是真正的赛车
I had no idea it was, like, you know, actual racing.
真是个比赛的好日子
It is a beautiful day for racing.
来一瓶吗
Hey, want a hit?
当然  谢谢  克里特
Sure. Thanks, Crit.
你们自酿的啤酒真给劲
This homebrew of yours is oh so refreshing.
你们的面包就
Your bread is,
哎呀  飞出去了
Whoop, hey, there it goes!
不小心飞出去了  不好意思
Got away from me there. Sorry about that.
-你  扔了它  -是的
- You-you kind of threw it. - Oh, yeah.
对  所以不是它飞出去了
Right. So it didn't get away from you.
-是你扔了它  -是的  很难吃
- You threw it. - No, it's bad.
我本来想照顾你的感受
I was trying to spare your feelings,
但如果你非要挑明说...
but if you want to address it,
-那面包确实不咋样  -得  我懂了
- it's not very good bread. - No, I get it. No.
得得得
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
我其实懂你意思
I guess I got it right away.
我只是觉得...算了
I just thought... forget it.
是啊  没必要为小事起争执
Yeah. Unnecessary little confrontation here.
吉恩  过去这几周里
Gene, you've been oddly enthusiastic
你对挥旗表现出了惊人的热情
about flag waving these last couple weeks.
我本以为你来捣乱的
I thought you were just messing with me,
没想到你是认真的
but you were serious.
认真得很
Very serious.
这样的话  我有件事
Then, well, there's something
要拜托你
I want to ask you.
天呐  你要死了
Oh, my God, you're dying!
我来继承你的衣钵
I'll take over for you!
-啥  不  我没有要死  -早晚会死
- What? No, I'm not dying. - For now.
我不会死
I'm not dying.
好吧
Okay.
我是想问你
I was gonna ask you
是否愿意首次尝试在大奖赛挥旗
if you wanted to flap your first grand prix.
非常荣幸
I would be honored!
我来帮你挥旗  格斯  但不会取代你
I'll wave your flag, Gus, but I'll never replace you.
行  我知道了
Right, I-I know.
声明一下  只是这一次哈
Just to clarify, it's only one race.
等着瞧吧
We'll see.
各位  快过来  饼干代酒
Guys, huddle up. Cookie toast.
蒂娜  把奖杯带回来
Tina, bring it home for us.
里科  这饼干十美元一个
Hey, Rico, these cookies are ten dollars each.
-别吃得好像只值五美元一样  -对不起
- You're eating them like they're five dollars each. - Sorry.
我能吃一个吗
Can I have a cookie?
我会把饼干放在终点线那里
I'll put a cookie on the finish line.
要是有人碾过去了呢
But what if someone drives over it?
那个人会是你
That someone will be you.
那我还是吃不了啊
Then I can't eat it.
又是你  布莱斯
Great. Bryce.
你来了  我不爱
You here, me no like.
给你的车来点意面沙拉
Pasta salad on your kart.
你竟敢在我的赛车上涂沙拉
Don't you put pasta salad on my kart!
车手们  离比赛开始还有两分钟
Drivers, two minutes to the start of the Grand Prix!
我会打败你  打败蒂娜
I'm gonna beat you! I'm gonna beat Tina!
打败你们这些富二代
I'm gonna beat all you Richie Riches!
不太可能  看那边
Not likely, especially because of that.
-我去  -我弹  我弹
- Crap. - Flick, flick.
是油泵坏了
It's a blown pump.
我没带工具
I don't have my tools,
我可以徒手试试
but maybe I can rig something.
车手们  请到起跑线
Drivers, to the starting line!
不知道来不来得及
I don't know if we're gonna make it!
可以的  可以的
We'll make it! We'll make it!
怎么了
What's going on?
看来你要少一名竞争对手了
It looks like you have one less competitor to beat.
可我不想用这种方式打败她
But I don't want to beat her this way.
今天  你用这种方式打败他
Today, you beat her this way.
明天  你用那种方式打败她
Tomorrow, you beat her that way.
重要的是今天你得打败她
All that matters is today you beat her this way.
-车手们  发动引擎  -好了
- Drivers, start your engines! - There!
会漏点油
Now you're gonna leak some oil,
但应该能撑完比赛
but you just might make it around!
谢了  克里特
Thanks, Critter.
对了  轮胎可能会掉下来
Oh, and a wheel mighfall off.
-啥  啥  -没啥
- What? What?! - Nothing!
别想东想西了
Get out of your head!
你是修好了没啊  克里特
Did you fix it or not, Critter?!
就当是修好了吧
Let's say I did.
上上上
Go, go, go!
拜托  碰碰赛车
Come on, bumper-kart!
往前冲  你可以的
Hold it together! You got this!
感觉怎么样
How you doing out there?
我在赢得比赛和赢回我妹妹的爱
Well, I'm torn between the desire to win
之间挣扎
and my love for my sister.
-当我没问  拜  -拜
- Forget it. Bye. - Bye.
好样的  甩掉那些势利小人
Atta girl. Let's beat these snobs!
好耶
Yeah!
好呀
All right!
吉恩  该挥白旗了
Gene, it's white flag time.
最后一圈了
Last lap coming up!
就是现在了  蒂娜  赶紧发力
It's now or never, Tina. Make your move!
超他
Pass him!
搞什么
Oh, come on!
嘿  那样可不好  布莱斯
Hey! That's not nice, Bryce!
所以才叫"不乃斯"呢
Oh, I get it now.
够了
That's it!
不可能
What?!
再见了  布莱斯  我的车记住你了
So long, Bryce. I kartly knew you.
快  快  布莱斯  冲啊
Go! Come on, Bryce, get it together.
蒂娜和露易丝在最前面
That's Tina and Louise out in front.
冲啊  姑娘们  拿下比赛
Come on, girls! Win this thing!
天呐  我还以为她俩都会输呢
Oh, my God. I assumed they'd both lose.
万一她们其中一人赢了另一人怎么办
What if one of them wins and beats the other?
不要让我去处理
Dibs on not handling it!
该挥方格旗了  他们来了
Checkered flag time! They're coming in!
吉恩  用两面挥
Gene, do the double!
我没准备好
I'm not ready!
放松  放松  深呼吸
Easy, easy. Deep breath.
用你的心去挥
Let it flow from within you.
他们来了
Here they come!
我去
Son of a bitch!
太好了  大奖赛冠军是我们的了
Yes! The Grand Prix is ours!
皇颅岛队冲啊
Go Team K.I.S.
贝尔彻赛车
不  是贝尔彻队冲啊
No, go Team Belcher.
等等  你说什么
Excuse me? What are you talking about?
你疯了吗  你要帮其它队赢吗
Are you crazy? You're helping another team win?!
抱歉  沙夏  这关乎亲情
Sorry, Sasha. It's a family thing.
他使"格斯"动作了
He's Gussin'!
-你干嘛呢  -帮你赢
- What are you doing?! - Helping you win!
赢的人该是你  你开得更好
You should win! You're the better driver.
你该赢  你好不容易才走到这一步
You should win. You worked really hard to get here.
确实  但是...好吧  我赢了
I guess, but... Oh, I just won.
旗挥得不错  吉恩
Nice flag-waving, Gene!
我做到了  我做到了  我挥旗成功了
I did it! I did it! I waved that flag!
好样的  孩子们
Yay, kids!
好耶  好耶  孩子们
Yes! Yes, kids!
干得好  就是这样
Yeah, that's the way to do it!
贝尔彻  贝尔彻  贝尔彻
Belchers! Belchers! Belchers...
没人么  没人喊
No one? No one.
早上六点十分
吃完了没  雨果
Are you done yet, Hugo?
听着  鲍勃  我们都知道你在卖私酒
Look, Bob, we both know you're slinging homebrew.
要不是我上司对我说
And if my supervisor wasn't saying,
"你要是再在那件案子上
"I'm going to fire you
浪费时间  我就解雇你"
if you waste any more time on that case,"
我肯定会逮到你的
I'd nail you for it.
不过  香肠还是不错的
That said... the sausages are good.
走吧  罗恩
Let's go, Ron!
剩下的薄饼能帮我打包吗
Hey, can I get a box for my pancake half?
给我直接塞嘴里  那点塞牙缝都不够
Just stuff it into your mouth! It's half a bite!
我们得打住了
We got to stop.
不能继续搞这个了
We can't keep this up.
谢天谢地  我好累
Oh, thank God. I'm so bloated and tired.
得有人去告诉泰迪
Somebody's gonna have to tell Teddy.
-我不要说  -我不要...
- Dibs on not telling him! - Dibs on not...
该死
Damn it!
你怎么能这么快
How do you talk so fast?
弯转得不错
Oh, good turn.
蒂娜  蒂娜
Tina? Tina?
你  你又在梦里开车了
You're-you're driving in your sleep again.
抱歉
Oh, sorry. Yeah.
我知道我俩都算冠军
I know it's like we both won,
但我们是不是可以不抱着奖杯睡觉了
but maybe we both don't need to sleep with the trophy, huh?
算了  最后再抱一次
Okay, one more night.
好的  最后一周  好梦
Okay, one more week. Sweet dreams.
*一路狂奔*
*Racing with the road*
*极速*
*Race*
*赛车*
*Fast*
*极速*
*Race*
*赛车*
*Fast*
*极速*
*Race*
*赛车*
*Fast*
*极速*
*Race*
*赛车*
*Fast*
*极速*
*Race*
*赛车*
*Fast*
*极速*
*Race*